(Amy:)Homespun stories, knowledge
of physics and a bosom that defies it.
(Amy:)You're the whole package,
aren't you?
Sorry I'm Iate. Ugh, I got great news.
(Howard(arriving):)NASA picked my team's design
for the deep field space telescope...
(Howard(arriving):)...that's going on the
International Space Station this spring.
Oh, woo, heh.
wow, heh.
- Howie, that's wonderful! Congratulations!
Uh, heh.
(Howard:)It gets better. Someone has
to go up with the telescope...
(Howard:)...as a payload specialist,
and guess who that someone is, heh.
Muhammad Li.
Who's Muhammad Li?
Muhammad is the most
common first name in the world...
...Li, the most common surname.
(Sheldon:)As I didn't know the answer, I thought
that gave me a mathematical edge.
(Howard:)It's me, Sheldon. It's me.
I'm going up in space!
(Howard:)Technically, I'm an astronaut.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
- Heh.
- Hang on a second.
NASA doesn't have a shuttle anymore.
- How are you gonna get up there?
- Oh, uh, it's cool.